(Bernadette:)Yeah, we just want to have
the kind of dinner
(Bernadette:)that we've all had here
so many times before.
(Howard:)Good food, good friends, and
sometime around midnight,
(Howard:)heartburn that makes
you pray for death.
(Amy:)Do you need any help
in the kitchen?
(Bernadette:)No, we got it. You guys
make yourselves comfortable.
(Penny:)All right, hey, you two, we're
here for Howard right now, okay?
(Amy:)Yes, so please
behave yourselves.
(Leonard:)Fine.
Of course.
(Stuart:)So I heard you two, uh,
wrote a paper together.
(Stuart:)How's that going?
(Penny:)This food is amazing.
(Raj:)Mm, and not
a vegetable in sight.
(Howard:)That's not true.
(Howard:)We've got tomatoes right here.
(Amy:)All these bright people sitting
around a table by candlelight.
(Amy:)Feels like we could be an
18th century French salon.
(Sheldon:)Indeed.
(Sheldon:)Penny, a salon is a gathering
(Sheldon:)where intellectuals
entertained each other
(Sheldon:)with sparkling conversations
about issues of the day.